（中央咖啡厅 今晚开放欢唱）
（中央咖啡厅）
# 因为每次我看到你的脸 #
# 'Cause every time I see your face #
# 就情不自禁的失态 #
# I can't help but fall from grace #
这个女的很棒
Wow. This girl's good.
是啊 有押韵的歌词 连我都没想过
Oh, yeah, a song with rhyming words. Ooh, I never thought of that before.
我喜欢她
I like her.
为什么因为她会唱歌 会弹吉他
Why? Because she can sing and play guitar...
然后将两个结合在一起
...and do both at the same time?
我对这些人的期望也大概就这么多
Well, that's pretty much all I'm looking for from these people.
看看你 好嫉妒喔
Look at you, all jealous.
别这样 菲比 你们两人的风格完全不同
Yeah, Pheebs, come on. You two have completely different styles.
她比较这样… 而你是…
You know, she's more... you know? And you're more:
# 说你会留在我身边 #
# Say you'll stay beside me. #
看吧 大家都很高兴她唱完了
Okay. See? See? Everybody else is happy she's done.
好 我下一首歌叫做
Okay, my next song's called:
"菲比•步非 我们说是非
"Phoebe Buffay, What Can I Say? I Really Loved When We Were...
我怀念搭档的过去 期许回去"
...Singing Partners and I Shouldn't Have Left You That Way."
不会吧 又是那种有隐藏意义的歌
Oh, no. One of those look-for-the-hidden-meaning songs.
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 纵有狂风暴雨 #
# When the rain starts to pour #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 支持一如往昔 #
# Like I've been there before #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
嘿 菲比
Hey, Phoebe.
嘿 莱丝莉
Hey, Leslie.
你怎么知道我会在这里
How'd you know I'd be here?
我在卖大鱼的地方碰见弗拉德…
I ran into Vlad at the place where they sell the big fish...
他说你常在这里表演
...and he said you played here a lot, so...
听好 我得去厕所
All right. I have to go to the bathroom.
如果她们又提到大鱼那个地方…
But if the place with the big fish comes up again...
我想知道是有好几条大鱼 还是只有一条大鱼
...I'd like to know whether that's several big fish or just one big fish.
菲比说你会写广告歌
So Phoebe tells us you write jingles.
我其实是说她抛弃我跑去写广告歌
Actually, I said she abandoned me to write jingles.
有没有我们会听过的
Uh, anything we might've heard of?
有
Uh, yeah, um...
# 家永远不远 #
# Home is never far away #
# 回家的感觉就是家星燉品 #
# Home is Homestar Stew #
对 但是我不写了 我变得很厌倦
Yeah, but I don't do that anymore. I got kind of sick of it.
想不出好的歌曲 所以他们炒我鱿鱼
And then I couldn't come up with anything good, so they fired me.
真惨
Hmm, bummer.
其实我…
Well, you know, I was just...
我在想说… 希望可以…
Um, I was just thinking and just hoping that...
或许你想跟我再次搭档
...maybe you'd want to get back together?
不要 不过谢谢你的提议
No, but thanks.
别这样 菲比 你可不可以考虑一下
Oh, come on, Phoebe. Would you just think about it?
好
Okay.
不要 谢谢了
No, but thanks.
好
Okay, uh...
再见了 菲比
See you, Pheebs.
真是残忍
Wow. That was kind of brutal.
好 希望大家都能学到教训
Well, okay. Let this be a lesson to all of you.
好吗 一旦背叛我 我就会变成冰雪女王
All right? Once you betray me, I become like the Ice Woman.
我会非常冷淡 冷酷 绝不让步
You know, I'm just very cold, hard, unyielding.
没有东西能穿透我冷硬的外壳
You know, nothing, nothing can penetrate this icy exterior.
可以给我一张卫生纸吗
Can I have a tissue, please?
好
Oh, yes.
有人在里面吗
Is someone in there?
没有 这只是一个冒险游戏…
No. This is just part of a daredevil game...
叫做"等到我膀胱爆掉死去"
...that I play called "Wait Until the Last Moment Before I Burst and Die."
天啊 你是掉到…你好
Jeez, man. Did you fall...? Hi.
有吗 你有掉到哪里去吗
So, uh, did you? Did you fall high?
有人在女厕 我等不及
Someone was in the ladies' room. I couldn't wait.
但是我有把马桶盖掀起来
- I left the lid up for you, though.     - Ha, ha.
噢 阿甘你先去吧
You know what, uh, Gunther? Go, uh... Go ahead.
我在跟…
I'm talking to, uh...
这时候你要说你的名字
This is the part where you say your name.
- 琴吉   - 我在跟琴吉说话 所以…
- Ginger.     - Ginger. I'm talking to Ginger, so...
- 你不用去厕所吗   - 不用
- Don't you have to use the bathroom?     - No.
不 我只是… 我情愿跟你讲话
No, I just, uh... I'd rather, uh, talk to you.
对 我需要
Yes, I do.
我得去上厕所
Yes, I do have to go to the bathroom.
里面有人
Someone in here.
- 钱德人呢   - 他来不了
- Where's Chandler?     - He can't make it.
他说他得回去工作…
He said he had to go back to his, uh, job to do, uh...
乔伊
Joey?
乔伊•崔比亚尼
Joey Tribbiani?
乔伊 我看得到你
Joey, I can see you, okay?
你躲在大衣后面
You're hiding behind the coats.
好险
Close one. Heh.
- 嗨   - 嗨 亲爱的
- Hi.     - Hi, sweetie.
哈罗
Hello.
嘿 罗斯
Hey, Ross.
- 我有坏消息   - 什么
- I've got some bad news.     - What?
我可以很快吃点东西 但之后得回来
I can get a quick bite, but I have to come back here.
别这样 你过去两个礼拜每天都加班
Come on, sweetie. You've worked late every night for the past two weeks.
- 这次又是什么事   - 是我的错 我今天辞职了
- What is it this time?     - It's kind of my fault. I quit today.
但是工作优先
But work comes first.
噢 真令人难过 怎么了
Oh, hey. But that's sad about you, though. What happened?
发生什么事 榨干精力 精疲力竭
What happened? Burn out? Burn all out, did you?
不是 他有更好的工作
No, he's leaving for a better job.
噢 太好了 那么再见了
Oh, well, that's great. So I guess this is, uh, goodbye then.
再见
Goodbye. Ha, ha.
- 好吧   - 好
- Okay, then.     - Okay.
我们都会想你的
Well, we're gonna miss you around here.
我也会想你们
Yeah, me too.
- 星期六见   - 没问题
- So see you on Saturday.     - Yeah, you bet.
你知道那在印度是很精致的东西吧
Now, you know those are a delicacy in India.
刚刚又是莱丝莉打来 看可不可以复合
Yeah, that was Leslie calling again to see if we can get back together.
今天打了差不多二十次 祝你好运 莱丝莉
It's like the 20th time today. Yeah, good luck, Leslie.
她一定很伤你的心吧
Wow. She must've hurt you pretty bad, huh?
是啊 我们以前是最要好的朋友…
Well, yeah. You know, we were best friends...
小时候 我们两个人的妈妈都在驳船上工作
...ever since we were little. Our moms worked on the barge together.
你们两个人在驳船上跑来跑去一定很可爱
You two must've been so cute running around on a barge.
绝不能在驳船上跑步
You never run on a barge.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
钱德在吗
Is, uh...? Is Chandler around?
不在 他在咖啡厅认识了一个女生
No, um, he met some girl at the coffeehouse.
好像叫做琴吉
Yeah. Ginger something.
不…
No.
不会吧 你确定不是 听起来像琴吉
No, no. Uh, are you sure it wasn't something that sounded liked Ginger?
像是"琴吉尔"
Like, uh, "Gingeer"?
不 是琴吉
No, it was Ginger.
我会记得是因为他告诉我时 我说…
I remember because when he told me, I said:
电影明星
The movie star.
该死
Oh, man.
我之前就是在躲那个女孩
That's the girl I was hiding from.
她如果知道他是我室友 一定会跟他说我做了什么
When she finds out he's my roommate, she'll tell him what I did.
- 你做了什么   - 噢 不 我不能…
- What did you do?     - Oh. Oh, no, no. I can't...
我不能说 那是我这辈子…
I can't tell you that. It's like the most awful, horrible thing...
- 做过最糟糕的事   - 这样吧 不要跟我们说
- ...I've ever done in my whole life.     - You know what? Don't tell us.
等钱德回来再说 那样比较好玩
We'll wait till Chandler gets home because it'll be more fun.
好吧
All right.
大概是四年前
Okay, it was, like, four years ago.
琴吉跟我约会了几次 有个周末…
Okay, Ginger and I had gone out a few times. Then one weekend...
我们去了她父亲的小屋…
...we went to her dad's cabin...
就我跟她和她烦人的小狗 胡椒
...just me, her and her annoying little dog, Pepper. Heh.
那一晚 我煮了一道很浪漫的晚赛…
Well, that night I cooked this really romantic dinner...
你在食物中下毒
You gave her food poisoning.
我还希望是如此
I wish. No.
晚餐后 我 她和小狗都在炉火前睡着了
After dinner, me, her and Pepper all fell asleep in front of the fire.
我在半夜醒来 看到火快没了
Well, I woke up in the middle of the night and I saw that the fire was dying out...
所以捡了一块木头 丢进去
...so I picked up a log and threw it on.
至少我以为那是块木头
Or at least what I thought was a log.
天啊 你把狗丢进去
Oh, my God. You threw Pepper on the fire.
我希望如此
I wish.
还有一件琴吉的事 我或许得告诉你们…
See, I guess another thing I probably should've told you about Ginger...
她有…
...is that she kind of has a, uh...
假肢
...artificial leg.
天啊
Oh, my God.
乔伊 你把她的脚丢到火里之后做了什么
Joey. What did you do after you threw her leg on the fire?
我就跑了
I ran.
那是我有过最棒的吻…
Well, that's the best kiss I've had...
至少跟在男厕认识的人是的
...with anybody I met in a men's room.
也是我最棒的吻
Actually, me too.
脚在水坑里 都弄湿了
Oh. Foot in a puddle. Foot all in the puddle.
该死 我最讨厌这样了
Oh, damn. I hate that.
我们得让你脱掉鞋子
We're gonna have to get you out of those shoes.
噢 不用担心
Oh, don't worry about it.
- 说真的 你会很冷   - 我不会
- No, really. You're gonna freeze.     - No, I'm not.
不会你有生化电子脚吗
Huh. You're not? What do you got, a bionic foot?
或许有一天会有吧
Someday. Maybe.
书很好笑吗
Funny book?
不是 我只是在想一件今天好笑的事
Hmm? Oh, no, no. I'm just thinking about something funny I heard today.
马克说了"星期六见"
Um, Mark saying, "I'll see you Saturday."
对 去听演讲
Yeah, at the lecture.
我上个礼拜就跟你说了 你说你不介意
I told you that last week. You said you didn't mind.
噢 不是 不是听演讲的关系
Oh, no, no, no. It's not the lecture, uh, I mind. Um...
拜托不要说是因为我跟马克去的关系
Oh, please tell me it's not because I'm going with Mark.
- 嗯…   - 天啊 罗斯
- Well...     - Oh, my God. Ross.
很抱歉 但是… 如果他不是你的同事了
Well, I'm sorry, but... Look, if you're not working with him anymore...
为什么还要跟他出去
...why do you still have to do stuff with him?
因为他是我的朋友
Because he's my friend.
好 但你真的需要多一个朋友吗…
Okay. But do you really need another friend? I mean...
好 如果我停止跟乔伊和钱德玩耍 就可以跟马克玩吗
Okay. Well, if I stop playing with Joey and Chandler, can I play with Mark?
这很好笑吗 我应该笑吗
Is that funny? Am I suppose to be laughing?
我不知道 你也觉得 "星期六见"很好笑
I don't know. You thought "See you Saturday" was funny.
马克是时尚业的人
Look, honey, Mark is in fashion, okay?
我喜欢有共同兴趣的朋友
I like having a friend that I can share this stuff with.
你们永远不会跟我去听演讲的
You guys would never go to a lecture with me.
我很想跟你去
I would love to go with you.
- 真的吗   - 对
- Really?     - Yeah.
嘿 我有衣服 我也会挑衣服
Hey, I have clothes. I even pick them out.
我也可以当个时尚…
I mean, for all you know, I could be a fashion...
贩子
...monger.
好 亲爱的 我会很高兴你跟我去
Okay. Honey, I would love for you to go with me.
怎么了
What?
我该穿什么 我开始紧张了
What should I wear? Now I'm all nervous.
有句话说 "有人看的锅子不会叫"
You know, they say, "A watched pot never beeps."
只是… 已经两个小时了…
It's, you know, ahem... It's been a couple hours...
她还没打来
...and she hasn't called.
也不是说我介意 我一点都不
Not that I even care. I don't.
菲比 你为什么不直接打给她
Phoebe, why don't you just call her?
你很明显想要打
You obviously want to.
你以为你很了解我
You think you know me so well.
- 你不想打吗   - 对
- Well, don't you wanna?     - Yeah.
- 好 所以我很了解你   - 我就是那样说啊
- Okay, so I do know you.     - That's what I said.
- 那么呢   - 我做不到
- Well, so?     - I can't.
做不到 她甩了我
I can't. She dumped me.
我超相信她的 然后突然有一天…
I mean, I totally trusted her, and then one day it was like:
"好 再见了 菲比" 就这样走了
"Okay, bye, Pheebs." Gone.
你知道最难过的部分是什么吗 我们一起弹奏的时光…
You know what the saddest part is? When we were playing together...
那是我最棒的时光 这辈子最棒的
...that was like the most fun I've ever had in, like, all my lives.
# 我最爱的鞋子对我真好 我每天都穿它 #
# My favorite shoes So good to me, I wear them every day #
# 就算鞋子磨破 我也不在乎 #
# Down at the heel, holes in the toes Don't care what people say #
# 我双脚最要好的朋友 #
# My feet's best friend Pals to the end #
# 穿上它显得我很辣 #
# With them, I'm one hot chickie #
# 但是有一晚 天不是很亮 #
# Though late one night Not much light #
# 我踩到黏黏的东西 #
# I stepped in something icky #
# 黏黏鞋 黏黏鞋 #
# Sticky shoes, sticky shoes #
# 总是让我微笑 #
# Always make me smile #
# 黏黏鞋 黏黏鞋 下次我会 #
# Sticky shoes, sticky shoes Next time I'll #
# 避开 #
# Avoid the #
# 屎 #
# Pile #
我们开始看到很多纱布和颜色层层搭配
We're beginning to see a lot of layering of sheer fabrics and colors.
举例说明 透明的海蓝色上衣搭在粉红色的…
For instance, a sheer navy blouse over a pink...
我很高兴我们来了
I'm really glad we came.
你好漂亮
You're so pretty.
我爱你
I love you.
# 臭猫 臭猫 #
# Smelly cat, smelly cat #
# 他们喂你吃了什么 #
# What are they feeding you? #
# 臭猫 臭猫 #
# Smelly cat, smelly cat #
# 这不是你的错 #
# It's not your fault #
哇 实在太棒了
Wow, that's great.
- 是吗   - 这可以大卖的
- Oh, yeah?     - You know, you could totally sell this.
很适合做猫砂广告
It'd be perfect for, like, um, a kitty-litter campaign.
广告歌 不要
A jingle? No, no, no.
为什么 你可以赚很多钱
Why not? You make a ton of money.
如果是为了钱 我现在早就是百万富翁了
Okay, if I was in this for the money, I'd be a millionaire by now, you know?
你不能再想广告歌曲的事了
You gotta get out of that jingle-head, sweetie.
你说得对 我很抱歉
Ugh. You're right. You're right. I'm sorry.
- 没关系   - 好
- That's okay.     - Okay.
好 现在我要弹奏一首很难过的歌
All right, I'm gonna play a song now that's really, really sad.
- 好   - 歌名叫做"搞混的魔术师盒子"
- Okay.     - Okay, it's called "Magician Box Mix-Up."
超大的手镯 超大的耳环…
Oversized bracelets, oversized earrings...
总之只要是超大的饰品 现在都很流行
...oversizing of accessories in general is very popular now.
- 嗨   - 嘿
- Hi.     - Hey.
这个可以借我吗 我的牛奶坏掉了
Oh, can I borrow this? My milk's gone bad.
我最讨厌那样了
Oh, I hate that.
我有次喝了低脂的 偷了我的车
I once had a thing of half-and-half. Stole my car.
你和琴吉的约会如何
So how was your date with Ginger?
很好 很棒 她很…
Great. Ahem. It was great. She's, uh...
她很棒 个性很好 很漂亮 就是很棒
She's great. Great looking, great personality. She's greatness.
听起来她…
Sounds like she's got the, uh...
整个人都很好
...whole package.
乔伊跟你说脚的事情了
Joey told you about the leg, huh?
天啊 我吓死了 我知道不该这样 但没办法
Oh, God. It freaked me out. Okay? I know it shouldn't have, but it did.
我不想停止见她 但偶尔会变成…
I like her. I don't wanna stop seeing her, but every so often, it's like:
"嘿 你的脚呢"
"Hey, you know what? Where's your leg?"
我是世上心胸最狭窄的人 对吧
I mean, I'm the smallest person in the world, aren't I?
我是世上心胸最狭窄的人
I'm the smallest person in the world.
早安
Morning.
其实他才是心胸最狭窄的人
Actually, he's the smallest person in the world.
听过烧脚的事了 对吧
Heard about the leg-burning, huh?
有提到
It came up.
我知道机会不大 但是…
Ahem, listen, I, uh... I know it's a long shot, but...
她有觉得还蛮好笑的吗
...by any chance, did she find that funny?
我是打盹了一下
So I nodded off a little.
打盹 罗斯 你还打呼
"Nodded off"? Ross, you were snoring.
我爸的船撞到岩石时都没发出那么大的声响
My father's boat didn't make that much noise when it hit rocks.
别这样 四十五分钟耶
Come on. Forty-five minutes.
那个人花了四十五分钟讲有背带的裙子
Forty-five minutes, the man talked about strappy-backed dresses.
那好 如果是在超冷的会堂里花四个小时…
Well, okay, how about four hours in a freezing museum auditorium...
听着皮蛋教授说…
...listening to Professor Pitstains and his:
"嘿 各位 还记得那个死了几千万年的东西吗
"Hey, everybody. Remember that thing that's been dead for a gazillion years?
我们不知道他有这根骨头"
Well, here's a little bone we didn't know it had."
首先 他是皮坦教授
First of all, it's Professor Pitain.
再来 那一小根骨头证明了…
And second of all, that little bone proved that...
那个恐龙有翅膀 但不会飞
...that particular dinosaur had wings but didn't fly.
好 你知道我刚刚听到什么吗
Okay, you know what I just heard?
几百万人会去戏院看我研究的东西
You know what? A hundred million people went to see a movie about what I do.
我在想会有多少人去看 叫做"侏罗纪大衣"的电影
I wonder how many people would go see a movie called Jurassic Parka.
噢 这实在太…
Oh, that is so...
不 不 不 一堆失控的大衣…
No, no, no. A bunch of out-of-control jackets...
占领了小岛
...take over an island.
如果我的工作这么无趣…
You know, if what I do is so lame...
你为什么还坚持要跟我去
...then why did you insist on coming with me this morning?
只是好让我不能跟马克去吗
Huh? Was it so I just wouldn't go with Mark?
不
No.
我…我想跟你在一起
I... I wanted to be with you.
我不知道 我觉得最近…
I don't know. I feel like lately...
你离我越来越远…
I feel like you're slipping away from me...
有新工作 新朋友
...with this new job and all these new people.
你有全新的生活
And you've got this whole other life going on.
我知道这很蠢…
I know it's dumb...
但我不喜欢自己不是你那个生活的一部分
...but I just hate that I'm not a part of it.
这不蠢
It's not dumb.
但或许你不是其中一部分也没有关系
But maybe it's okay that you're not a part of it.
你懂吗
You know what I mean?
我喜欢你不属于我那个生活的一部分
I mean, it's like I like that you're not involved in that part of my life.
这样清楚多了
That's a little clearer.
这不代表我不爱你…
Honey, see, it doesn't mean that I don't love you...
因为我真的很爱你
...because I do. I love you. I love you so much.
但我的工作是另一回事
But my work, it's for me, you know?
我自己在外打拼
I'm out there on my own, and I'm doing it.
很可怕 但我很喜欢 因为是我的工作
And it's scary, but I love it because it's mine.
但是…这样可以吗
But I mean, is that okay?
当然可以
Sure. Ha, ha.
你在想我的脚 对吧
You're thinking about my leg, aren't you?
不是
No, no.
其实我忘掉了发生了什么事
Actually, I forgot. What is the deal with that again?
如果让你很困扰也没关系
Look, it's okay if it bothers you.
我只需要知道 有多困扰你…
I mean, the only thing I need to know is how much it bothers you...
因为我不想浪费我的时间
...because I don't like wasting my time.
我在浪费我的时间吗
Am I wasting my time?
- 不 我不这么认为   - 好
- No. No, I don't think so.     - Okay.
跟其他事情一样 你只是得习惯
It's just like anything else. You just have to get used to it.
那是什么
What's that?
那是我的小点
That's my nubbin.
什么是小点
What's a nubbin?
有点像… 第三个奶头之类的
It's kind of a, uh... A third-nipple kind of thing.
你有三个奶头
Do you have three nipples?
嗯 有两个是正常的…
Well, you know, two regulars, ahem...
有一个勉强算是奶头
...and, uh, one that barely qualifies.
- 怎么了   - 没事 我…
- Uh, what?     - Nothing. I...
我刚想起来我得走了
I just remembered. I have to leave.
你现在得走了为什么
You, uh...? You have to leave? Now? How come?
嗯 是奶头… 没事
Well, it's nubbin. Nothing.
我们晚点再见 好吗
Um, you know what? I'll see you later. Okay.
我以为你不来了
Oh. I thought you weren't coming.
- 你去哪了   - 过来
- Where were you?     - Come here. Come here.
好 不要生我的气喔
Okay. Don't get mad, okay?
不要给我生气的理由 好吗
Okay, don't give me a reason to get mad, okay?
我弹奏"臭猫"给我的旧广告公司听 他们超爱的
I played "Smelly Cat" for the people at my old ad agency. They went nuts.
听好 我说过我不要你这么做
No, look. I told you that I didn't want you to try and sell it...
你还是给我做了
...and you just big fat did it anyway.
天啊 你知道吗 五年前…
God. You know what? I think, five years ago...
我可能会竭尽所能 只为了跟你一起演奏
...I probably would have done anything to play with you.
但我可以自己来 如果我不能相信你 那就算了
But I can do it by myself, right? And if I can't trust you, then just forget it.
不 我不要算了
No. No. I don't wanna forget it.
好 你得做出选择
Okay, you know what? You have to choose.
如果这世上对你最重要的事情…
All right? If the most important thing on the planet to you...
是猫大便那类的东西 那首歌可以给你
...is this cat-poopy thing, then, okay, you can have "Smelly Cat."
但我们不会是搭档
But we won't be partners.
你怎么说
So what's it gonna be?
- 臭猫 臭猫   - 猫砂盆很臭吗
- Smelly cat, smelly cat     - Odor in the litter box?
不要换掉你的小猫 换掉你的猫砂
Don't change your kitty. Change your kitty litter.
# 这不是你的错 #
# It's not your fault. #
- 我很遗憾  菲比   - 对
- Sorry, Pheebs.     - Yeah.
你还好吧
You okay?
嗯 我真的还好
Yeah. I actually am. Yeah.
因为生命会有各种考验
Because, you know, life's gonna hand you all kinds of stuff.
学到教训后 希望能有所成长
You know, you learn your little lessons and hopefully you grow.
想听首新歌吗
You wanna hear a new song?
- 好   - 好啊
- Yeah.     - Oh, we'd love to.
好
Okay.
# 广告歌婊子骗了我 #
# Jingle bitch screwed me over #
# 去死吧 广告歌婊子 #
# Go to hell, jingle whore #
# 去死吧 去死吧 去死吧 #
# Go to hell, go to hell, go to hell #
目前只写到这里
That's all I have so far.
大家好啊
Well, hello.
- 你去哪了   - 看医生
- Where have you been?     - The doctor.
- 没事吧   - 没事
- Is everything okay?     - Oh, yes.
只是移除了小点
Just had me a little nubbin-ectomy.
没错 两个奶头 等不及了
Yep. Two nipples, no waiting.
就像高中的瑞秋
Well. Just like Rachel in high school.
什么
What?
少来了 我只是开玩笑 很明显是笑话啊
Come on. Come on, I was kidding. It was such an obvious joke.
的确是明显的笑话
That was an obvious joke.
我没想到 为什么没想到
And I didn't think of it. Why didn't I think of it?
我能量的泉源
The source of all my powers.
天啊 我做了什么
Oh, dear God, what have I done?